

ALBERTO CARLOS CASTRO CASTRO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have participated in different projects at an industrial level. More than 8 years of career in which I have worked with multiple programming languages and frameworks I have specialized in Java. Use of agile methodologies (Scrum), UML artifacts as a tool for software modeling, Modeling in databases.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Java SE, EE, Spring, Hibernate, JPA, Reactor
- 00P
- · PHP experience.
- Database: Mysql, Oracle, CosmosDB
- MVC, Web Services, REST, SOAP
- Functional Programming
- VCS (SVN-Git-Github)
- CI/CD(Jenkins)
- · Testing and Refactoring.
- UML
- AGILE METHODOLOGIES: SCRUM
- Experience with cloud platforms (AWS, Azure)

OTHER SKILLS

- Understanding the "big picture" beyond implementation details
- · Great capacity for self-learning
- Good communication and time management
- Ability to work in a team
- Assertive communication
- Implement improvements to increase software efficiency and effectiveness

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: 304-6730359 Skype: carloscastro010

Linkeid: https://www.linkedin.com/in/cazcode

Email: ingcastro214@gmail.com

Medellin, antioquia

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Development Analyst Java Personalsoft S.A.S | 2018 - Present

- Implementation of new technologies that allow the solution of problems submitted by the client
- Administrator of software resources that contribute to the optimization of the management of business information.
- Responsible for analysis and development based on the application architecture.
- General knowledge of business operation.
- Implement cloud solutions for database and software deployments

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Development Analyst Java Corplas S.A.S | 2016 - 2018

- Responsible for analysis and development based on the application architecture.
- General knowledge of business operation.

JUNIOR ENGINEER

Development Java Corplas S.A.S | 2015 - 2016

- Responsible for analysis and development based on the application architecture.
- Applications support and in-house developments are provided

EDUCATION HISTORY

UNIVERSIDAD DE CARTAGENA

Pending college degree

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

- CURSO DE PROGRAMACIÓN FUNCIONAL CON JAVA SE (IN PROGRESS)
- JAVA 8 SE 2019
- MASTERY IN JAVA WEB SERVICES IN LESS THAN 3 HOURS!-2019
- JAVA SERVLETS AND JSP BUILD JAVA EE(JEE) APP IN 25 STEPS-2019
- TEST DRIVEN DEVELOPMENT CON JAVA Y JUNIT5 2019
- CERTIFICATION MICROSOFT HTML5, CSS Y JAVA SCRIPT